Aika,
小爱
aren't you being a little impulsive today?
你今天是不是有点太冲动了
Hmm, I'm sorry.
嗯 对不起
It's okay, but why did you do that?
没关系 不过你为什么要那么做啊
I don't know either.
我也不知道
Did you remember our classmates came to my house a few days ago?
前阵子班上同学不是来我家吗
Yeah, Airi is so cute.
嗯 小爱莉有够可爱的
Airi was very close to Sasaki at the time.
那时候爱莉跟佐佐木同学很亲近
So, I wanted others to…
所以也想让其他人…
Huh? Is it not good for Airi to be close to him?
咦 小爱莉跟他亲近不好吗
It's not that it's not good.
倒也不是不好啦
I see.
原来如此
So, you didn't want it to be like this?
原来你不喜欢这样啊
You don't want others to get ahead of someone
你不希望其他同学抢先某人
and get too close to Airi, right?
跟小爱莉走得太近对吧
So, did you see Sasaki and then think of Sajo that day?
所以那天的小佐木 让你联想到小佐城了吗
D-Don't say anymore…
你别再说了…
Sajo hasn't been looking for you lately.
最近小佐城都不来找你了
It's like he's trying to hurry you up.
总觉得他好像让你心烦意乱
B-But I'm not sure why I would have such thoughts.
但…我也不知道 为什么自己会有这种想法
Sajo must be like a safe haven
小佐城对你来说
in your heart for you, right?
一定像是你心中的避风港吧
How could he be a haven?
他怎么可能是避风港
He's always pestering me. It's annoying.
他老是缠着我 有够烦人
I'm not talking about whether it's comfortable when you're together.
我并不是在说相处的时候是否舒服
Isn't it nice to be liked by someone?
有人喜欢自己 不是一件很令人开心的事吗
T-This…
这个嘛...
Anyone would feel insecure
如果突然失去了一个避风港
if they suddenly lost a safe haven, wouldn't they?
任谁都会感到不安吧
Kei, you see things so clearly.
圭 你看得真透彻
But I think these clumsy parts
不过 我觉得你这种笨拙的地方
of you are also very cute, so I like you.
真的很可爱 所以我很喜欢
Stop it, don't make fun of me.
讨厌 你别嘲笑我了
Sorry, sorry.
抱歉抱歉
But Sajo might not
不过 小佐城也不一定
always be by your side.
会一直待在你身边吧
At least Sajo has always
至少小佐城
shared his true feelings with you.
一直以来都有对你说出他的内心话
He says it every day, which is so annoying.
每天说到我都烦了
Isn't it your turn to act this time?
所以这次是否该轮到你做点什么了呢
-Huh? -Give me a sip. Let's exchange.
-什么 -给我喝一口 我们交换吧
-Wait a moment. -The chocolate flavor is also really good.
-等等 -巧克力口味也好好喝
(Dark brown? Sounds quite cool)
（暗棕色？听起来很帅气）
You're a bit sloppy.
你这样有点邋遢耶
Well, I'm just sloppy.
反正我就是邋遢啦
-No, I mean your hair. -Huh?
-不是 我是说你的头发 -啊？
Wow, it's grown so long now.
哇 都这么长了
Your hair is obviously layered, so you should go dye it evenly soon.
发色都已经分层得这么明显了 你快去染均匀
-This is called two-tone dyeing. -What?
-我这叫双层发色 -啊？
Don't you think it's rather fashionable?
你不觉得这样反而很时髦吗
What are you talking about? This will only make people think it is dirty.
你在说什么鬼话 你这样只会让人觉得很脏
To look good, light-colored hair must be dyed with care.
亮色系发色就得好好整理
Yeah, I will dye it when the time comes.
哦 我到时候会去染啦
You used to pay more attention to your appearance.
你之前明明就很在意仪容
Yeah.
是啊
Before, in order to become a man worthy of Natsukawa,
之前我为了成为配得上夏川的男人
I made all kinds of efforts.
做了各种各样的努力
Now, I just feel that caring too much is useless.
现在我只觉得太在意也没用
I'm not trying to get close to anyone.
我又没有想跟谁走得很近
Good morning, Natsukawa.
早安 夏川同学
Why are you suddenly so formal?
你干嘛突然这么拘谨
Do you think I can be the same as usual
昨天发生了那种事
after what happened yesterday, my goddess?
您觉得我还能像平时一样吗 女神大人
Good morning, Natsukwa and Ashida.
早安夏川 还有芦田
You just said hello to me in passing, jerk.
你只是顺便跟我问好吗 混蛋
Don't kick my calves.
别踢人小腿啊
Did you guys get home safely yesterday?
你们昨天有平安到家吗
We went to try the new Starbucks drink.
我们去喝了星冰乐的新商品
-Right? -Huh? Yeah.
-对吧 -啊 嗯
You guys had a lot of fun.
你们玩得很开心嘛
It was especially quiet without you, which was wonderful.
多亏你不在 耳根很清净
Of course.
那当然了
After all, it was a girls' gathering.
毕竟是女生聚会嘛
It's so hot, Sajo. Can you fan me?
好热 小佐城你快给人家搧搧风嘛
You're good at ordering people around. I really can't handle you.
就只会使唤人 真拿你没办法呢
This scorching sun is unbearable.
炎炎烈日真让人受不了
Oh my, I don't know if my sunscreen is enough.
讨厌 不知道防晒乳还够不够
You guys, stop messing around. It's disgusting.
你们别闹了啦 有够恶心
NO NEED TODAY. GOT IT.
(今天不用了) (收到)
YOU DON'T NEED TO COME AND HELP TODAY
(今天也不用你帮忙)
That is fantastic. I always think it would be awkward if Senior Yuki was present.
太好了 我总觉得有结城学长在会很尴尬
The window seats are usually occupied, but are they empty today?
平常窗边位置都会坐满人 今天居然空着
Can I sit here? Really?
我可以坐这里吧 没问题吧
Today at the convenience store, I bought two nutrition bars instead of one.
只要吃一条就能饱足的营养棒 我今天在便利商店买了两条
Again, there are two nutrition bars and a loaf of bread!
我再说一遍 两条营养棒再加上面包
I might have a nutritional surplus today, but I really can't control myself.
我今天大概会营养过剩吧 但我真是难以克制自己
Look at the back. Are you Sajo?
看这背影 你是佐城吧
Oh… Hi…
啊…哈啰 你们好啊
Wait a minute.
且慢
How come you started eating again?
你怎么就若无其事地吃了起来
You should normally ask us, "Is it convenient to share a table?"
正常来说 你应该问我们要不要并桌才对吧
No need. Your team is a little frightening, isn't it?
不用了 你们这组合有点吓人吧
Whatever way you look at it, the student council is terrifying.
风纪委员团体 无论怎么想都让人心生恐惧
Who's that angel over there?
这位天使是谁啊
Please correct yourself, it's an archangel.
请你更正一下 是大天使
You're looking so serious.
你的眼神好认真
Sajo! Come eat with us.
佐城学弟 你来跟我们一起吃嘛
Huh? What?
咦 什么？
Yuyu said so. Did you get it?
由结都开口了 你知道该怎么做吧
Yes.
啊 是的
Sajo, what are you eating?
佐城学弟 你在吃什么啊
Just a loaf of bread I bought from the convenience store.
就是一些在便利商店买的面包
Geez. You can't just eat that. You need to eat something healthier.
真是的 你这样不行啦 要吃有益健康的东西才对
Yes… huh?
哦好…咦？
-Could it be that you got a boyfriend? -No way.
-难道学姐她交男朋友了吗 -怎么可能啊
My ears, my ears…
我的耳朵我的耳朵...
They're going to fall off!
要断掉了要断掉了...
No way.
怎么可能嘛
I'm sorry.
对不起
Is this your first time meeting Aya, Sajo?
佐城学弟你是第一次见到小绫吧
She's my childhood playmate.
她是我的儿时玩伴
She is an excellent junior. She's the one who educated Yuyu so well.
就是这位优秀的学妹 把由结调教得如此出色
-That's really impressive. -Yeah.
-那还真是厉害 -还好
Aya, why are you being so distant?
小绫你真是的 怎么这么冷淡
I-I didn't.
我…我才没有
Smile, smile quickly.
你就笑一个嘛 笑一下
Nice to meet you.
请多指教
You don't have to force yourself.
你不用勉强自己啦
To be clear, everything I did was for Yuyu, not for you.
我话说在前头 我这么做 都是为了由结 不是因为你
Aya.
小绫！
Listen,
你听好了
men are perverts who only have lewd eyes
男人都是变态 只会戴着有色眼镜
for cute girls like Yuyu.
打量像由结你这种可爱的女生
Sajo is not that kind of person.
佐城学弟不是那种人
That's right, because Sajo is a coward.
没错 因为佐城是个孬种
Senior, can you not say hurtful things all of a sudden?
学姐 你别突然说出伤人的话好吗
-It's really good. -Yeah, looking forward to it tomorrow.
-好好吃呀 -是啊 好期待明天的这个时间
-Humph. -What's wrong?
-哼 -怎么了吗
How do you feel seeing Yuyu's change?
看到由结的变化 你觉得如何？
Of course, I was shocked.
我当然是吓了一大跳
Did you let her play some otome game?
你是让她玩了什么少女游戏吗
How could I let her play that kind of game? Yuyu is my wife.
我怎么可能让她玩那种游戏 由结可是我老婆
What about Senior Mita?
那三田学姐呢
She's her mother.
是她妈妈
I see.
原来如此
You didn't tell Senior Inatomi, did you?
你没跟稻富学姐说吧
Do I need to?
我有必要说吗
Not really.
也没有
But I thought you would ask me
但我还以为学姐你会让我
to stay away from Senior Inatomi.
再也不要靠近稻富学姐呢
How could I do something like that?
我怎么可能做那种事
I will never abandon my benefactor who helped me change Yuyu.
我绝对不会抛弃 帮我改变由结的恩人
What? Benefactor?
什么恩人
Yes, what's important for Yuyu now is
没错 对于目前的由结而言重要的是
to know that the boys she is afraid of also have their merits.
要让她知道 她害怕的男生这种生物也是有优点的
First, we need such an opportunity.
首先需要一个这样的契机
Opportunity…?
契机啊...
Yes, the words you spoke to Yuyu
没错 当时你对由结说过的话
at the time instilled confidence in her.
让她有了自信
Her confidence grew as a result,
在那之后
and she had the courage to take a step forward.
她的自信心大增 有了迈出一步的勇气
I didn't do anything significant.
我也没做什么了不起的事情
On the contrary, it was a good thing you did,
不如说 你这样做正好
it was just right for her who's overly negative.
对于过度消极的她来说恰到好处
Whatever the method, you, Sajo,
不论过程如何
are the one who provided Yuyu with this chance.
就是佐城你给了由结这个契机
It was pure coincidence,
只是凑巧而已啦 而且
and I am not sure I will ever talk
我以后应该再也不会像那样
to girls so casually again.
轻易找女生说话了
It's okay.
无所谓
That won't have any negative impact.
那样也不会产生什么坏影响
Didn't it have a good impact this time?
这次不就产生了好的影响吗
Yes, if we only look at the results.
只论结果的话是没错啦
Be confident, Sajo.
佐城 你要有自信一点
Confident?
自信吗
You not only helped Yuyu,
你不仅帮了由结
but you also helped me solve a problem.
也帮我解决了烦恼啊
Huh? Did I do something?
咦 我有做什么吗
Yes, I did as you suggested
嗯 我照你所说
and patted my junior's shoulder, saying, "Do not worry about it."
拍拍学妹的肩膀 说了一句“别放在心上”
Then Yuyu happily leaned on me. That's really…
然后由结就开心地靠在我身上 那可真是…
Restrain yourself, Senior.
学姐 你克制一点
But I had no idea you were Kaede's younger brother.
不过真没想到你就是枫的弟弟啊
So you know my sister?
学姐你果然认识我老姐吗
Yes, we met in first grade.
嗯 一年级刚开学时我们就认识了
Is it that time when my sister decided to dye her hair blonde
就是我老姐在开学第二天染金发
on the second day of school in order to become a hot girl?
决心化身辣妹的那时候吗
She really gave me a lot of trouble then.
那时候她可是给我添了不少麻烦
Well, as her younger brother, I apologize to you on her behalf.
该怎么说呢 由我这个做弟弟代她向你道歉
(Dreaming Boy is a Realist, The)
《满怀美梦的少年是现实主义者》
Sasaki? Are you feeling unwell?
佐佐木 你身体不舒服吗
BROTHER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(哥哥 你在干嘛？)
ARE YOU CHATTING WITH SOMEONE? WHO IS WITH YOU?
(在跟谁聊天？跟谁在一起？)
Oh, it's Yuki. How has she been since then?
是小有希啊 后来她怎么样了
I saw her carrying a primary school backpack when I got home.
我回家就看到她背着小学生书包
No, forget what I said. Anyway, she keeps sending me these when I'm not home.
不 当我没说 总之只要我不在家她就会狂传信息
Please accept my condolences.
请节哀顺变
Who do you think is responsible for this?
你也不想想这是谁害的啊
NEW MESSAGES, MISSED CALLS But,
(新信息 未接来电) 不过
your sister is quite cute like this.
你妹妹这样还满可爱的啊
Sajo, you also have a sister, right?
佐城你也有姐姐吧
Yes, I have one.
嗯 我家那一只
Does she treat you gently because she's your older sister?
她会因为是姐姐就温柔对待你吗
Sometimes the relationship is so complex that it is difficult to put into words.
这种关系的确有点复杂 无法一言以蔽之
Great, you understand me so quickly.
太好了 你这么快就明白了
Knowing you have such a sister
话说回来 你明知道你妹妹会这样
but still making a move on Natsukawa's sister is where you went wrong.
却还对夏川的妹妹动心 这就是你的不对了
Not at all! My target is not Airi!
才没有 我的目标不是小爱莉
Whenever there's a limited new product, I can't resist wanting to try it.
一有什么限定新品 我就会忍不住想喝
Could you step aside for a chat?
我想借一步说话
Hmm, alright.
哦 好啊
I see.
这样啊
That's your reaction?
你的反应就这么平淡吗
I don't meddle in others' affairs.
我不会对别人的事情多嘴
Is there anyone on this planet who doesn't like Natsukawa?
再说这世上没有人会不喜欢夏川吧
I don't know about that, but Sajo, you haven't…
这我是不知道 但佐城你还…
It's Natsukawa who needs to make the decision, right?
要做决定的是夏川本人吧
I don't have the right to stop you.
我可没有权利阻挠你
But I will be super indifferent to you.
但我会对你超级冷漠
You will be indifferent to me?
你干嘛对我冷漠啊
You would dislike a man if he appeared next to your favorite idol, right?
自己喜欢的偶像身边要是蹦出个男人 你也会讨厌他吧
Sajo, I'm serious about going after her.
佐城 我是认真要追求她的
Why are you so passionate?
你热血个什么劲啊
What is Sasaki worrying about?
佐佐木是在担心什么啊
Natsukawa is the person I support the most.
夏川可是我最推崇的人啊
I've always known that this day would come.
我早就想过会有这么一天来临
I am not going to fantasize about an unreachable flower
我已经不会再妄想 像夏川这种高不可攀的女孩
like Natsukawa having any story with me any longer.
会跟我有什么发展了
But
但是
I still want Natsukawa
我还是希望夏川能跟一个
to be with a man who convinces me.
能让我心服口服的男人在一起
Does Sasaki deserve Natsukawa?
佐佐木配得上夏川吗
At the very least, he doesn't appear to be a bad person.
他应该不是什么坏人就是了
Let me scrutinize you from head to toe.
就让我彻头彻尾地审视他一番吧
Sasaki has already won the affection of Airi.
佐佐木已经得到了小爱莉的喜爱
And he's a handsome guy.
又是个帅哥
I guess I better not get close to
我果然还是不要再靠近
Natsukawa anymore.
夏川比较好
Sajo.
佐城
Can you please return these assignments from the next class for me?
这些作业混到隔壁班去了 你帮老师发还一下
Why me?
为什么是我
Because you're the closest, please.
因为你离得最近嘛 麻烦你了
Alright…
啊 好的…
Natsu…
夏…
-Natsukawa, did you see that too? -Yes.
-夏川你也有看那个吗 -嗯
Oh. Ashida, help me give this to Natsukawa.
啊 芦田 你帮我把这个给夏川
Sajo, why don't you do it yourself?
你干嘛不自己去啊
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
抱歉 我很急
What? Bathroom? Run!
急着上厕所吗 快去快去
Thanks.
谢了
Do you need me to do the rest, too?
剩下其他的也要我来吗
There's no one inside.
里面没人哦
I don't need to go.
我没有要上啦
Natsukawa? What's the matter? You're so cute.
夏川？怎么了 真可爱
I-I'm not cute.
我…我才不可爱
Didn't you just go home with Ashida and the others?
你刚不是跟芦田他们一起回家了吗
Huh? How did you know?
咦 你怎么知道
I just happened to see it. Did you forget something at school?
我刚好看到的啦 你是忘了什么东西吗
Yes, something like that.
啊 嗯 算是吧
Be careful, it's already late.
时间不早了 你要小心点哦
I'll go with you.
要我陪你一起去吗
Did you find it?
找到了吗
Yes, don't rush me.
啊 嗯 你别催我嘛
It's good you found it.
找到就好
What's wrong?
你怎么了
By the way, I have something to ask you.
话说回来 我也有事要找你
Huh? You have something to ask me?
咦 有事找我？
I-It's not a big deal.
也…也不是什么大事啦
I promised Kei to ask you this today.
只是我跟圭约好了 要在今天问你这件事
What is it?
什么事
Wh-Where do you go during lunch break?
午…午休时间你都去哪里啊
Huh? I eat on the courtyard bench at times and in the cafeteria at other times.
嗯？我有时候会在中庭的长椅吃饭 要不就是去食堂吃
W-With whom?
跟…跟谁一起呢
Just me.
就我一个人啊
Why do you eat alone?
你为什么要一个人吃饭
I mean, isn't it nice to eat with others?
我是说 跟大家一起吃不好吗
Yeah, but today I ate with the student council members.
啊 不过我今天是跟 风纪委员那些人一起吃的
Senior Shinomiya, Inatomi and…
四之宫学姐跟稻富学姐还有…
Senior Shinomiya?
四之宫学姐？
Huh? Yeah.
咦 对啊
Why? What's your relationship?
为什么 你们是什么关系
We just met by chance.
就刚好遇到而已
What kind of relationship?
什么关系...
Just a regular senior-junior relationship.
就一般的学姐学弟关系吧
And she's my sister's friend.
然后她是我老姐的朋友
I-I see…
这…这样啊…
What's with this awkward atmosphere?
这个尴尬的气氛是怎么回事
-What about us? -Huh?
-那我们呢 -什么
Can't you eat with us like you used to?
你不能像以前一样跟大家一起吃饭吗
Huh? You mean…
啊 大家是指…
Well, this…
嗯 这个嘛...
Our relationship has changed slightly as a result of my deliberate distance.
由于我的故意疏远 让我们的关系产生了某些变化
In fact, Natsukawa has made new friends now.
实际上 夏川现在也交到了新朋友
Natsukawa's youth may be jeopardized
我要是继续待在夏川身边
if I continue to be by her side.
就有可能会破坏她的青春
Should I support Sasaki's love affair
从这一点来考虑的话 关于佐佐木的恋情
in light of this?
也许我真的该支持一下吗
I absolutely don't want to.
我才不要
Oh no! I mean, I absolutely don't want to know the final exam results.
啊不是 我是说 我才不要知道期末考的成绩
What do you think about this, Natsukawa?
关于这部分 夏川你觉得咧
What are you talking about?
你在说什么啊
You should do something about your hair.
你不打理一下你的头发吗
My hair? My sister also said I'm sloppy.
这个吗 我老姐也说我很邋遢
First impressions of you can vary greatly.
这会影响别人对你的第一印象
You should do something about your hair right away.
你还是早点处理一下比较好吧
On my way home, I will stop by the cosmetics store.
回家路上我会去趟药妆店
Which do you think looks better, black or brown hair?
你觉得黑发跟棕发哪个好看咧
That varies from person to person.
那因人而异吧
True, which do you think looks better? Brown or black hair?
也是啦 那你觉得我适合棕发还是黑发呢
Huh? Didn't I just…
咦 我刚不是…
Wasn't that a general opinion?
那是一般性的意见吧
What I want to know is what you personally think, Natsukawa.
我想知道的是夏川你个人的想法
You're just irresistible, Natsukawa.
你就是这点让人欲罢不能啊 夏川同学
Ahh. The fragrance coming from her body.
啊啊 她身上散发的淡淡清香
-Hmm. -H-How is it?
-嗯 -怎…怎么样
I think either one is fine.
我觉得两种都好
You can't answer just like that.
哪有人这样的
-Ah, but… -Hmm?
-不过... -嗯？
If you had brown hair back then, I probably wouldn't have talked to you.
如果那时候你是棕发 我可能就不会找你说话了
Back then?
那时候？
Then I'll dye it according to Natsukawa's preference.
那我就依照你的喜好染头发了
I-It's not exactly a preference.
这…算不上是喜好吧
I'm fine with any color.
我本身也是哪种颜色都可以
Did you hear that? That's not my preference.
你听好了 那算不上是我的喜好
I got it.
我知道啦
Wow, there's no black left.
哇 没有黑色了
Dark brown?
暗棕色？
Sounds pretty cool.
听起来很帅气耶
Do I have to stay still like this for twenty minutes?
还得这样静置二十分钟吗
It stinks. Didn't I tell you to close the door?
臭死了 我不是叫你把门关上吗
I can't touch the doorknob because my gloves are covered in hair dye cream.
我手上都是染发剂 哪关得了
Dark brown?
暗棕色？
Since there was no black, I chose this.
因为没有黑色我就选了这个
That's pretty good, it's super black when you first dye it.
那还不错啊 刚染完发色会超级黑哦
Really?
是吗
The dyeing is so bad, it's not even.
技术有够糟 根本不均匀
Get out of the way.
你让开
Thank you…
谢谢…
Hmm? Rubber gloves? I have a bad feeling.
橡胶手套？我有不祥的预感
-Ah, wait! -I asked you
-啊 等等 -我就说
not to be so careless with your hair dye.
染发不能这么随便
It hurts, don't rub so hard, you are ripping out my hair!
好痛 你别搓这么用力 会掉头发耶
-Your hair won't fall out. -It hurts!
-你的头发才不会掉 -好痛
-How is it? -Hmm, hmm…
-如何？ -嗯…
Isn't it a little too black?
这会不会有点太黑了
Didn't I just say it? It will be this black for now.
我刚不就说过了 暂时都会这么黑
But as long as you shampoo hard,
不过只要用力洗头
it'll feel natural in a couple of days.
大概两天就会变得比较自然
You are indeed a former blonde hottie.
不愧是染过金发的辣妹
I'll hit you.
你欠揍哦
FIRST SEMESTER, END-OF-TERM EXAM, RANK Enthusiasm.
(第一学期 期末考 名次) 积极性
It's constantly affecting everyone's motivation.
它是无时无刻 影响着每个人行动的原动力
Children run around outside with enthusiasm gushing out of their bodies.
孩童靠着内心涌出的积极性 在外面四处乱跑
Some junior high students try to fulfill their enigmatic dreams.
初中生则是沉浸在神秘幻想中 并设法将其化为现实（部分人群）
Then people go through adolescence and fall in love,
然后经历青春期 体验了感情的萌芽后
thinking about the person they admire and boiling with enthusiasm.
就会把因想起倾慕对象 而沸腾的那股热情
Then sublimation into their own motivation! Especially for boys.
升华为自己的原动力 尤其是男生
In short, what I want to express is,
总而言之 我想表达的就是
falling in love is quite amazing.
坠入爱河这件事真的很厉害
I ranked 32nd in the midterm exam.
期中考时我是第32名
I know why I regressed.
退步的原因我心里有数
I had a steely determination at the time to catch up with Natsukawa no matter what.
那时的我怀抱钢铁般的意志 无论如何都要追上夏川
Furthermore, our school's college entrance rate was previously very high.
再说我们学校升学率本来就很高
If it wasn't for my obsession with Natsukawa,
要不是因为对于夏川的执着
I wouldn't have been able to get into this kind of school.
我根本考不上这种学校
In other words, hmm…
也就是说 那个...
Compared to the last time,
比起上一次
this time I clearly lacked enthusiasm for studying.
这次我明显缺少了学习的积极性
Sajo, what's your rank?
小佐城你第几名啊
Did you crumple the paper?
你把纸揉掉了？
Sorry, sorry.
抱歉抱歉
I am 74th.
我是第74名哦
Is this your trick?
你这招是...
"I've told you my rank, so you have to tell me yours"?
“我都告诉你名次了 所以你也得告诉我”？
See, my grades have fluctuated a lot.
你看吧 我的成绩大起大落
Huh? Sajo, wasn't your last rank higher?
咦 你上次的名次应该更高吧
I'm not sure, I've forgotten.
不清楚 我也忘了
I thought you definitely ranked among the top 50,
我还以为你又会考进前50名
so I asked you.
我才来问你的
Unexpected.
真令人意外
So, is your ranking 76th good or bad?
那你这第76名是算考好还是考坏啊
It's 74th!
我是第74名
Got it, got it.
好好好
Why are you so proud?
你为什么一脸自豪样
Do you recall what rank I received the last time?
你还记得我上次第几名吗
I don't remember.
不记得了
220th! I've improved a lot, haven't I?
第220名！我进步很多吧
So you were a fool.
原来你以前是个笨蛋啊
Past tense! Seeing that you use the past tense, I'll forgive you.
看在你用过去式的份上 我姑且原谅你
Hi, Sajo, what was your ranking? I ranked 230th.
哟佐城 你第几名啊 我第230名哦
I wish I could be a fool like you.
真羡慕你能活得这么开心
Ah, um.
啊 嗯
FIRST PLACE, SHINONOME CLAUDINE MARIKA Our idol and goddess.
(第1名 东云克劳蒂娜茉莉花) 我们的偶像兼女神
Natsukawa Aika.
夏川爱华
She still maintains her excellent grades, as always!
她还是一如既往地成绩优异
What is he doing alone?
他自己一个人是在干嘛
I remember when I ranked 32th, Natsukawa ranked 27th.
我记得之前我第32名的时候 夏川是第27名
Did I indeed disturb her exam revision before?
以前我果然妨碍她读书了吗
Is the top student an international student?
第1名的是留学生吗
Aika. Share half with me.
小爱你分我一半啦
Share what with you?
分你什么啦
Hmm… what should I share?
嗯…要分什么好呢
If it were the old me, I would certainly have joined them.
换作是以前 我一定会加入她们
However, it's not bad to watch Natsukawa from a distance like this.
但像这样远远望着夏川其实也不错
Natsukawa, you've grown. As your fan, I'm incredibly honored.
夏川 你成长了啊 身为你的粉丝我真是无比荣幸
Sajo.
佐城
What's wrong, Sasaki? Finally stolen by your sister?
怎么了 佐佐木 终于被你妹妹偷走了吗
What was stolen?
偷走什么啊
Stolen your heart.
偷走你的心
No, I meant to talk about the exam ranking.
才不是 我是要说考试的名次
You aren't here to talk about your sister?
你居然不是要聊跟妹妹有关的事
Look.
你看
29TH PLACE, SASAKI TAKAAKI
(第29名 佐佐木贵明)
You're doing well.
真有你的
Right?
对吧
Are you the one who can't keep up now? Hmm?
反而是你开始跟不上了是吗
You dare to provoke me.
你竟敢挑衅我
Your mockery of others is as lovely as a painting. You are extremely irritating.
就连挖苦别人的模样都能美得如画 真令人不爽
Now the situation is serious.
这下事态严重了
For an unattractive student like me,
像我这种不帅的学生
my only weapon is academic subjects.
唯一的武器就是各种文科项目
In other words, studying.
也就是读书
Now, a handsome soccer club member is taking away even this advantage of mine.
我的这项优势 现在居然被足球队的帅哥抢走了
I can hardly accept it.
实在是令人难以接受
My enthusiasm has been completely stimulated,
完全激发出了我的积极性
and it exceeds my expectations!
而且远远超出我的预期
I hope in the future,
祝你从今以后
all your passes are offside!
所有传球都越位
You really say some harsh things.
你这人说话也太狠毒了吧
-I understand. -Hmm.
-我懂 -嗯
Oh, you dyed your hair.
啊 你染头发了
Hey, Sajo, are you okay?
喂小佐城 你没事吧
I just feel like you're so cute that I'm about to suffocate.
我只是被出其不意的可爱 吓到差点窒息了